---
questions:
# 1st question
  - question: "TechGears Inc., a company that manufactures high-end computer components, recently partnered with RetailWare, a nationwide electronics wholesaler, to distribute its products to various retail stores across the country. RetailWare, known for supplying numerous retail chains, will handle the bulk distribution of TechGears Inc.'s products." Which type of business transaction best describes the relationship between TechGears Inc. and RetailWare?
    answers:
    - "B2B (Business-to-Business)"
    - "B2C (Business-to-Consumer)"
    - "D2C (Direct-to-Consumer)"
    correct: 0

# 2nd question
    - question: "Ethan runs a growing online store for handmade crafts and wants to improve his website's functionality and appearance without delving into extensive custom development. He decides to explore different types of extensions to achieve his goals.
    Ethan’s objectives are:A. Enhance the site's functionality by integrating a new email marketing tool and adding a live chat feature for customer support.
    B. Improve the visual appeal by updating the site’s layout to be more user-friendly and visually consistent with his brand.
    C. Add a new feature for customers to calculate shipping costs directly on the product page.
    Which types of extensions should Ethan use to meet his objectives?"
    answers:
    - Apps, Themes, and Plugins
    - Themes, Plugins, and Apps
    - Plugins, Apps, and Themes
    - Apps, Plugins, and Themes
    correct: 0

# 3rd question
    - question: "TekUniverse wants to boost their visibility on search engines to attract more tech enthusiasts to their site. What would be your first step using Shopware to achieve this?"
    answers:
    - "Utilize Shopware’s built-in SEO tools to optimize the site, ensuring higher search engine rankings."
    - "Hire an SEO expert to handle the website optimization."
    - "Promote the site on social media to increase traffic."
    - "Redesign the website with a new look to attract visitors."
    correct: 0

# 4th question
    - question: "TekUniverse wants to boost their visibility on search engines to attract more tech enthusiasts to their site. What would be your first step using Shopware to achieve this?"
    answers:
    - "Utilize Shopware’s built-in SEO tools to optimize the site, ensuring higher search engine rankings."
    - "Hire an SEO expert to handle the website optimization."
    - "Promote the site on social media to increase traffic."
    - "Redesign the website with a new look to attract visitors."
    correct: "Utilize Shopware’s built-in SEO tools to optimize the site, ensuring higher search engine rankings."

# 5th question
    - question: "TekUniverse wants to create a secret page on their website that only VIP customers can access. This page will offer exclusive discounts and early access to new products. How would you set up this secret page using Shopware’s features?"
    answers:
    - "Create a hidden link that only VIP customers know about."
    - "Use Shopware’s customer-specific pricing and personalized shopping experiences to restrict access to the page for VIP customers only."
    - "Make the page visible to everyone, but hide the discounts."
    - "Use a secret handshake at the checkout to apply discounts."
    correct: "Use Shopware’s customer-specific pricing and personalized shopping experiences to restrict access to the page for VIP customers only."

# 6th question
    - question: "What is a key advantage of Shopware being an open-source platform?"
    answers:
    - "It provides a controlled environment for code modification and access."
    - "It facilitates community-driven development and allows extensive customization."
    - " It includes comprehensive support services directly from the software publisher."
    - " It necessitates subscription fee for all users."
    correct: "It facilitates community-driven development and allows extensive customization."

# 7th question
    - question: "Which Shopware plan would be most appropriate for a large enterprise with extensive customization needs?"
    answers:
    - "Shopware Community Edition (CE)"
    - "Shopware Evolve"
    - "Shopware Rise"
    - "Shopware Beyond"
    correct: "Shopware Beyond"

# 8th question
    - question: "Which Shopware plan would be most appropriate for a large enterprise with extensive customization needs?"
    answers:
    - "Shopware Community Edition (CE)"
    - "Shopware Evolve"
    - "Shopware Rise"
    - "Shopware Beyond"
    correct: "Shopware Beyond"

# 8th question
    - question: "What is a key advantage of choosing the Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) model over Software-as-a-Service (SaaS)?"
    answers:
    - "Automatic updates and minimal customization"
    - "Greater customization and control over data and applications"
    - "Complete control over hardware and software"
    - "Lower costs due to less technical expertise required"
    correct: "Greater customization and control over data and applications"

# 9th question
    - question: "You are the IT manager for a growing eCommerce business that has recently transitioned to Shopware. The company is now looking to enhance its online store with several key features: integrating advanced analytics to track customer behavior, adding multiple payment options to cater to different customer preferences, and updating the site's design to reflect a new brand identity. You need to determine the best Shopware extensions to address these needs. To address the needs of integrating advanced analytics, adding diverse payment options, and updating the site's design, which combination of Shopware extensions would be most effective?
    answers:
    - "Apps for advanced analytics, Plugins for payment options, Themes for design updates"
    - " Themes for advanced analytics, Apps for payment options, Plugins for design updates"
    - "Plugins for advanced analytics, Themes for payment options, Apps for design updates"
    - "Apps for advanced analytics, Themes for payment options, Plugins for design updates"
    correct: "Apps for advanced analytics, Plugins for payment options, Themes for design updates."

# 10th question
    - question: "In the context of eCommerce, what is the primary function of a Product Information Management (PIM) system?"
    answers:
    - "To track and manage customer interactions and relationships across various touchpoints."
    - "To create, manage, and modify digital content on a website without requiring technical knowledge."
    - "To manage and ensure consistency of product data across all selling platforms and channels."
    - "To oversee the fulfillment of orders, including tracking sales, inventory, and shipping processes."
    correct: "To manage and ensure consistency of product data across all selling platforms and channels."
---